<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[An Artist working on audio & visual arts]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[An Artist working on audio & visual arts]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 03:25:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="undefinedrss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bio]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Bio</h1><p>Born in Istanbul, Yiğit introduced himself to music at 4 via mandolin. He took a break and made a comeback with piano at 5th grade, which became his main instrument. Due to his diverse interest in other art forms he decided to study Visual Communication Design [BA] in Istanbul while still keeping his touch with music. This gave him a strong foundation in visual media, which makes him more of a filmmaker than just a traditional composer. After graduation, between studying “film” or “music” he decided to go towards ‘music for film’. Thus in 2008 he applied to and was admitted to Columbia College Chicago‘s ‘Music Composition for the Screen’ MFA program, where he had a chance to do some intensive work with industry professionals like Andy Hill and Hummie Mann expanding his vision and improving on necessary skills. On his last semester, where he moved to Los Angeles, CA, he had chance to work with Eimear Noone and Mike Reagan. This short semester was concluded with a recording & mixing session of his thesis project which took place at the legendary Capitol Records studios, for the original soundtrack of the short, Marilyn’s Dress. After moving to Istanbul, Turkey he worked as a composer on TV ads, films and video games whilst forming the alternative rock band Plüton’u Kurtarmak.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5607acb121aded8e7a11e3e089dffaad7ba612ff.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>undefinedbio/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">df5ae7d0-9962-4e1b-94d6-6cf2781e57b1</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2016 03:25:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>